Bradbury, M. mss. III 1950-2000 LMC 2695
Lilly Library
- Dangerous Pilgrimages – notes & research material (Box 84)
- Class work – Anthology of UEA stories for Hodder, 1995 (Box 84)
- TV Play "Love on a Gunboat" scripts, reviews, etc. (Box 84)
- Atlas of Literature – Mapping (Box 85)
- Dangerous Pilgrimages – page proofs from Secker (Box 85)
- Pemberton Billing and the Little Black Book (Box 85)
- Dimension Detective – IMAX screenplay (Box 85)
- After the Show – rehearsal script – ABC–TV, 1959; (2ff.) (Box 85)
- Furling the Flag – scripts (Box 86)
- In the Red – 3 episodes scripts – BBC–TV (Box 86)
- Tamara – research material for TV script (Box 86)
- Literature and Sociology – key off prints (Box 87)
- Dalziel and Pascoe – publicity files (Box 87)
- Gravy Train – Series 1 and 2 (Box 87)
- British Association for American Studies – correspondence (Box 88)
- Private Press items "Important" (Box 88)
- Correspondence –, 1978; 1990s–2000 (Box 88)
- British Council Literature Advisory Committee – Memorandum (mostly), (2ff.) (Box 88)
- Christmas cards, 1999 (Box 88)
- Josipovici, Gabriel. The Air We Breathe (Box 88)
- Barthelme, Donald. Forty Stories (Box 88)
- Benedictus, David. Floating Down to Camelot (Box 88)
- Touch of Frost – 3rd draft 7 Script amendments (Box 88)
- Touch of Frost/Keys to the Car – TV (Box 88)
- various scripts by others, (4ff.) (Box 88)
- Postmodernism – essays, conference papers, etc. (Box 89)
- TV screenplays (Box 89)
- Scripts of TV plays written with Chris Bigsby – The After Dinner Game, Stones (Box 90)
- MB & Chris Bigsby – Stones – TV play for BBC (Box 90)
- MB & Elizabeth B – draft scripts – William Cooper: Scenes from Provincial Life and Scenes from Married Life, David Storey (?) This Sporting Life – radio (Box 90)
- Morse – The Wench is Dead – TV (Box 91)
- Rates of Exchange – Film version by James Cellan Jones (Box 91)
- Spy Club – Muscovy Films – TV (Box 91)
- Blott on the Landscape – drafting filming, publicity – TV (Box 92)
- Pemberton Billing and the Black Box – material, TV (Box Pemberton Billing and the Black – material, TV)
- Angus Wilson book material?, etc. (Box Pemberton Billing and the Black – material, TV)
- Modernism and late Victorianism – notes/drafts/clippings (Box Pemberton Billing and the Black – material, TV)
- Useful articles: many topics including new novel, post modernism, etc. (Box 93)
- Modern British Novel, 2000–2001; (2 boxes) (Box 93)
- New Writing – writings & correspondence, (3ff.) (Box 94)
- The Eighties: Heroes & Villains – interviews/articles about (Box 94)
- Eighties Programme (Box 94)
- Motion, Andrew. Philip Larkin (Box 94)
- Contemporary Writer's – correspondence, etc. (Box 94)
- The Penguin History of Literature (Box 94)
- Barker, Raffaella. Come and Tell Me Some Lies (Box 94)
- Simons, Kosti. slow Sam and Downright Harry (Box 94)
- Spurling, John. Graham Greene (Box 94)
- Ziegler, Heide. John Barth (Box 94)
- Misc. papers (Box 94)
- Millennium library – Disc 1 (Box 94)
- Multimedia – Disc 2, Cold War, etc. (Box 94)
- Millennium library – Disc 2 (Box 94)
- The Modern World/Ten Great Writers (Box 95)
- What is a novel – work on proposed revision, John Fletcher – not completed (Box 95)
- American Lit. expatriates – research/BBC3rd Programme material, etc. (Box 96)
- Touch of Frost – The appendix Man – shooting scripts, TV (Box 96)
- Gravy Train 2, key MSB version (Box 96)
- Atlas of Literature – spreads (Box 96)
- Furling the Flag – script version (Box 97)
- Rates of Exchange – script BBC version (Box 97)
- Articles by MSB – magazines (Box 97)
- Teaching notes – Chaucer to C18th (Box 98)
- Teaching notes – Romantics to C20th (Box 98)
- Doctor Criminale – TV versions (Box 99)
- American novel in the 1920s (Box 99)
- Ezra Pound – Imagism (Box 99)
- Bibliographies, etc. on Postmodernism for teaching (Box 99)
- Bibliographies, etc on Postmodernism and creative writing (Box 99)
- The Denuded Place: The First World War and fiction (Box 99)
- Swizzlewick in Progress (Box 99)
- See a friend This Weekend (Box 99)
- A Very Hospitable Person – TV play, (2ff.) (Box 99)
- EC Commission scandal – clippings (Box 99)
- Film info sheets (Box 99)
- Angus Wilson book (Box 99)
- The Prostitute's Padre – Playhouse play (Box 99)
- Pig and Pepper (Box 99)
- Revision for BAAS pamphlet (Box 99)
- The Outland Dart: American Writer's & European Modernism, (2ff.) (Box 99)
- Misc. (Box 99)
- Early radio and TV writing (Box 100)
- Anything More Would Be Greedy, orig. series for Anglia TV, revised scripts, Ep. 1–6 (Box 100)
- Blott on the Landscape, BBC TV, shooting script (Box 100)
- The Gravy Train, Series 2, The Economic Market (TV) (Box 101)
- Introductions to books (Box 101)
- Radio & TV plays, early, Girl from Hillsley (radio), A Very Hospitable Person (radio), See a Friend This Weekend (radio & TV) (Box 101)
- Creative writing MA stories –, 1978–1981; 1983,… (Box 101)
- Gravy Train Goes East – scripts (Box 102)
- Roosevelt & Churchill – special relationship – TV (Box 102)
- Creative writing MA stories, 1983/1984 (Box 102)
- Porterhouse Black – possible TV project (Box 103)
- Flush – screenplay (Box 103)
- Doctor Criminale – versions of TV script (Box 103)
- Various pages of notes – unsorted (Box 104)
- Scenes from Provincial Life – stage version (Box 104)
- Writing for TV – lectures, etc. (Box 104)
- Scenes from Provincial Life – TV scripts (Box 105)
- In the Red – 3 x 50 min. episodes from BBC (Box 105)
- Early articles by MB – clippings, magazines, (2ff.) (Box 105)
- Rao, Ranga. Land of Regrets: Contemplative Comedy, Narayan's Gunas Comedy (Box 106)
- Stevens, Elisabeth. Ride a Bright and Shining Pony (Box 106)
- Oakley, Ann. Overheads (Box 106)
- various odd pieces (Box 106)
- MacBeth, George. The Long Darkness (Box 106)
- Hyman, Saul. Jacaranda Blues (Box 106)
- Levine, Paul. E.L. Doctorow (earlier version) (Box 106)
- Contemporary Writers series, (3ff.) (Box 106)
- John Fletcher: Robbe–Guillet (Box 106)
- Methuen series text, Ronald Meyman, Gunther Grass (Box 106)
- Methuen series, Joanne V. Creighton, Margaret Drabble (Box 106)
- Prager, Emily. A Visit from the Footbinder (Box 106)
- Doughty, Louise. Crazy Paving (Box 107)
- Contemporary Writers, by MB and Chris Bigsby. Uncorrected proofs, (10 vols.) (Box 107)
- Correspondence, 1970s–1990s; (4ff.) (Box 107)
- Golding, William. The Paper Men (Box 107)
- Dunn, Suzanne. Darker Days than Usual (Box 107)
- Ford, Richard. The Sportswriter (Box 107)
- Federman, Raymond. The Twofold Vibration (Box 107)
- Clayton, John J. Bodies of the Rich (Box 108)
- Knowlton, James and Jerome Klinkowitz. Peter Handke (Box 108)
- Burgess, Anthony. Enderby's Dark Lady or No End to Enderby, (3ff.) (Box 108)
- Misc. papers and letters (Box 108)
- Dangerous Pilgrimages/3. American writers and Europe (Box 108)
- Dangerous Pilgrimages/2: European 19th writers and American (Box 108)
- Complex Fates: The Expatriate tradition in American literature, 2nd copy (Box 108)
- Expatriates in London 1900+ (Box 108)
- Expatriates/London 1860–1900 (Box 108)
- Pound/Imagism/etc. Expatriates (Box 108)
- Dangerous Pilgrimages: Henry James & Europe (Box 108)
- James/Wharton (Box 108)
- Mark Twain (Box 108)
- Misc., (2ff.) (Box 108)
- Malcolm's teaching – at conferences UEA America, Europe etc. – time Yale, Harvard, Yaddo, (3ff.) (Box 108)
- Russian seminar/Cambridge (Box 108)
- The Appeal of Comsmopolitanism: Longfellow and American Artists after 1815 (Box 109)
- Hawthorne/Brook (Box 109)
- Hawthorn essay: A Rogue Among Detectives (Box 109)
- Hawthorne. prelim lecture/Boris Ford book (Box 109)
- Evelyn Waugh and Hollywood (Box 109)
- Clippings, (2ff.) (Box 109)
- Great Writers: Eliot (Box 109)
- Great Writers: Pirandello (Box 109)
- Great Writers: Franz Kafka (Box 109)
- Recent scripts for BBC radio (Box 109)
- Furling the Flag (TV) (Box 109)
- Cold Comfort Farm (TV) (Box 109)
- In the Red (TV) (Box 109)
- IMAX: Dimension Detectives (Box 109)
- Kavanagh, QC (Box 109)
- Dalziel and Pascoe: Ruling Passion and Killing Kindness (TV) (Box 109)
- Dalziel and Pascoe (TV) (Box 109)
- Touch of Frost 2 (TV) (Box 109)
- Miscellaneous papers (Box 109)
- Raphael, Frederic. The Glittering Prizes. Plater, Alan. The Land of Green Ginger. scripts (Box 110)
- Costa, Astrid Masetti Lobo. The Reflected Vision: A Study of the Role of Painting in the Development of Plot in Iris Murdoch's Novels (thesis), Nov. 1978 (Box 110)
- Lobo, Suely Maria de Paula e Silva. Places of the Mind: a study of Place Imagery in Muriel Spark's Novels (thesis)., Aug. 1980 (Box 110)
- Corker, D.T. Summary (Box 110)
- Rates of Exchange. Film version, (2ff.) (Box 110)
- Rates of Exchange. TV version, (3ff.) (Box 110)
- UEA courses (Box 110)
- Martin, Richard. Ideal and reality in the writings of E.M. Forster. MA thesis (Box 110)
- Misc. writings, (2ff.) (Box 110)
- Heroes and Villains, BBC–2 TV program… (Box 110)
- Kaleidoscope, etc. [correspondence] (Box 110)
- Critic's Forum (Box 110)
- The Powers of Time, radio talk (Box 110)
- Kingsley Amis, Take a Girl Like You (Box 110)
- various broadcasts (Box 110)
- TV ideas: The student, Delivery Date (Box 110)
- TV idea: A goodbye for Evadne Winterbottom (Box 110)
- Milkey report (Box 110)
- Melville and Hawthorne (Box 110)
- Chapter Nine [and] Chapter Eleven/Pilgrimage (Box 111)
- Possibilities – proof, (3ff.) (Box 111)
- Sharpe, Tom. The Midden – typescript, (2ff.) (Box 111)
- Miscellaneous writings by others, (2ff.) (Box 111)
- ____, Richard. X–20 – typescript (Box 111)
- Neuhaus, Denise. The Christening – proofs, (2ff.) (Box 111)
- Ramsay, Gordon P. [various writings] (Box 111)
- Rose, Margaret. Parody: ancient, modern and post–modern –proofs (Box 111)
- Graham, Kenneth. Hokusai's Wave – typescript (Box 111)
- Lasko, Peter. The Professor is missing – typescript (Box 111)
- various writers. book of short stories (Box 111)
- Clouston, J. Storer. His First Offence – photocopy (Box 112)
- Travel – Danube cruise, 1994 (Box 112)
- Harper, Graeme. Moon Dance – typescript copy, (2ff.) (Box 112)
- Miscellaneous writings by MSB and others, (2ff.) (Box 112)
- UEA/Centres/New Appeal (Box 112)
- Arthur Miller Centre – UEA (Box 112)
- Centre for Creative and Performing Arts (Box 112)
- Booker seminar, UEA (Box 112)
- UEA publicity (Box 112)
- Course – Disintegration of Victorian Synthesis (Box 112)
- Lectures/ New OED, FCO/Britain in the World (Box 112)
- Lecture and article – Age of Parody (Box 112)
- Lecture – How literary is literary criticism (Box 112)
- Lecture – Writing American literary history (Box 112)
- Creative writing book – …materials (Box 112)
- Creative writing students – recent (Box 112)
- Pretext/UEA Centre (Box 112)
- Creative writing/info/courses, etc. (Box 112)
- Article on literary criticism (Box 113)
- Literary criticism – Leicester – work with P.A.W. Collins, etc. (Box 113)
- UEA creative writing (Box 113)
- Introduction American studies (lecture notes) (Box 113)
- History as fiction, fiction as history/ lecture notes, article… (Box 113)
- MA creative writers – past years (Box 113)
- Early writings from creative writing course (Box 113)
- Info. about MA in creative writing (Box 113)
- UEA creative writers (Box 113)
- Creative writing/organizational (Box 113)
- See a Friend – materials (Box 113)
- Scenes from Provincial Life, (2ff.) (Box 113)
- Note: This idea led to The History Man and also The After Dinner Game (Box 113)
- Unsorted manuscript pages (Box 113)
- Early articles, etc. (Box 113)
- The American city in literature, (Summer 1976) (Box 113)
- Lecture: London as culture capital (joint course, etc.) (Box 113)
- City and country in literature (Box 113)
- Modernism: London essay (Box 113)
- Notes for culture capitals – London, Greenwich Village (Box 113)
- Matters to deal with in University (Box 114)
- Modernism and the Culture Capitals (Box 114)
- Golding, William (Box 114)
- Assorted papers/pamphlets, … (Box 114)
- Mss.–TV materials (Box 114)
- History Man – radio treatment (Box 114)
- Mss. proofs (Box 114)
- Introductions, etc. (Box 114)
- Lectures, etc. (Box 114)
- Rates of Exchange, (2ff.) (Box 114)
- See a Friend (Box 114)
- Love on a Gunboat – printed (Box 114)
- unidentified writing (Box 114)
- Ian McEwan/Kazuo Ishiguro (Box 114)
- Rushdie, Salman (Box 114)
- Magic realism (Box 114)
- Lessing, Doris (Box 114)
- Fowles, John (Box 114)
- Wilson, Angus, (2ff.) (Box 114)
- Roy Hudd Show, Yorkshire TV (Box 114)
- The Forced Marriage (Box 114)
- Patterson, (2ff.) (Box 114)
- Bowler, Tom (Box 114)
- Misc. (Box 114)
- Dangerous Pilgrimages: Wilde, Crane, Aesthetes (Box 115)
- Expatriates (Box 115)
- Chapter Eight/Pilgrimages. Hemingway, Paris in the 20s (Box 115)
- Chapter Seven/Pilgrimages. Stein, etc. (Box 115)
- Larkin, Philip (Box 115)
- Murdoch, Iris, (2ff.) (Box 115)
- Amis, Kingsley,; John Wain, (2ff.) (Box 115)
- Sixties – important reviews (Box 115)
- British fiction in the Sixties (Box 115)
- Scenes from Provincial Life, working material (TV) (Box 115)
- Rates of Exchange. TV version/correspondence (Box 115)
- Expatriates book. Draft text, USA (Box 115)
- British Council seminar brochures (Box 115)
- Christmas cards and, 1997; 1998; (2ff.) (Box 115)
- Contemporary writers – uncorrected proofs, (2ff.) (Box 115)
- Reprints, (3ff.) (Box 115)
- Lurie, Alison. The War Between the Tates – proofs (Box 116)
- The British Council. Correspondence, etc., (3ff.) (Box 116)
- UEA – BA and MA examinations, (3ff.) (Box 116)
- The Novel Today – reviews & permissions (Box 116)
- Possibilities – drafting of the text (Box 116)
- The Green Man – revised scripts, (2ff.) (Box 116)
- Doctor Criminale – correspondence (Box 116)
- VC's reports on MSB (Box 116)
- Job applications (Box 116)
- Applications for posts (Box 116)
- Bellagio visit. June 1987, details (Box 116)
- Major lecture engagements (Box 116)
- Literary prizes: Angel and others (Box 116)
- Modern American Novel. Proofs (Box 116)
- Longman Series (active) (Box 117)
- A History of American Literature (Box 117)
- No, Not Bloomsbury (Deutsch essays) (Box 117)
- Collected essays (for Tom) (Box 117)
- Mailer, Norman (Box 117)
- Pynchon, Thomas (Box 117)
- Singer/Malamud/Henry Roth (Box 117)
- Salinger (Box 117)
- Unsent Letters. Text and background (3ff.) (Box 117)
- Modern American Novel – revisions (Box 117)
- All Dressed Up and Nowhere to Go (Box 117)
- Arnold booklet: The Novel (Box 117)
- Modern American Novel – revision (Box 117)
- Introduction to American studies (general) (Box 117)
- Formal speeches/ UEA, etc. (Box 117)
- Speeches for dinners, etc. (Box 117)
- Indiana University Wells Professor, 1997; (2ff.) (Box 117)
- Introductions to: EPIW/Stepping Westwards/ The After Dinner Game (Box 118)
- Stepping Westwards – reviews (Box 118)
- Eating People is Wrong – reviews (Box 118)
- Travel – American trips (Box 118)
- UEA honorary degrees (orator) (Box 118)
- Curtis Brown (Box 118)
- Atlas of Literature – writers or places (Box 118)
- Atlas of Literature – good material (Box 118)
- Introductions to books (Box 118)
- MBN/Beckett, Nouveau Roman (Box 118)
- Booker Prize (Box 118)
- British Novel in the 50s (Box 118)
- Fiction of the 80s and 90s (Box 118)
- Book introductions – recent/drafts (Box 118)
- William Cooper article – 'Novel' symposium (Box 119)
- Everyman's Library – introductions (Box 119)
- Everyman introductions (paperbacks) (Box 119)
- Dalziel & Pascoe – Fox on the Run (Box 119)
- Dalziel & Pascoe – new script (Box 119)
- Drama House/Suspicion (Box 119)
- Literary letters book (Unsent Letters) (Box 119)
- Literary letters – pieces used, (2ff.) (Box 119)
- History of American Literature – Chapter four (Box 119)
- Flaxborough chronicles (Box 119)
- The Good Book Guide (Box 119)
- Encyclopedias/editorial advising (Box 119)
- Excelsior Group Productions Ltd. – Tono–Bungay (Box 119)
- Swan Hellenic cruise – lectures/Italy, etc., (2ff.) (Box 119)
- The Gravy Train – notes for a novel version (Box 119)
- American masters (Box 119)
- A Suitable Vengeance – BBC TV (Box 119)
- Modern British Novel – Joyce (Box 119)
- Bloomsbury – clippings (Box 119)
- Symbolism/aestheticism/decadence (Box 119)
- Early 20th Centry Poetry (Box 119)
- To the Hermitage – research/background, etc. (Box 119)
- Diderot at the Hermitage (Box 119)
- Macmillan/new publication (Box 119)
- Curriculum vitae –, 1998 (Box 119)
- Swan Hellenic, (4ff.) (Box 119)
- Publications, etc. (Box 120)
- TV projects/new proposals (Box 120)
- The Modern British Novel – revision (Box 120)
- Material for MB's readings (Box 120)
- Macmillan reissues – other titles (Box 120)
- Book proposals/ Penguin, etc. (Box 120)
- Hermitage – publication (Box 120)
- Modern British Novel – Henry James, Joseph Conrad (Box 120)
- Modern British Novel – Lawrence, Bennett, Wells, etc. (Box 120)
- Theory of Fiction (2) character, etc. (Box 120)
- Modernisms/Postmodernisms – Hassan, etc. (Box 120)
- BBC radio series – The Radical Years (Michael Mason) (Box 120)
- Modernism – some essays and reviews by MSB and reviews by others (Box 120)
- Modernism – bibliographies (Box 120)
- Modernity and modernism – course (Box 120)
- The Booker of Bookers, 1993 (Box 120)
- Booker Prize, 1981, 1983 – MSB chairman, (2ff.) (Box 120)
- Booker (recent) (Box 120)
- Booker – management committee (Box 120)
- The Modern World – LWT/Channel 4 (Box 120)
- Expatriates: Colonial Lit. Culture/Chap & notes (Box 120)
- Expatriates book – various notes for introduction (Box 120)
- Observer article – filming Fitzgerald (Box 120)
- Background for articles – TV, Culture, etc. (Box 120)
- Clippings/(state of) Contemporary novel (Box 120)
- Clippings – BBC TV (Box 120)
- New Yorker article (Box 120)
- Broadsheets/arts (Box 120)
- Articles on Europe and the EC – New York Times/ Britain, etc. (Box 121)
- Reference guide to short fiction (Box 121)
- Modernism and the magazines (Box 121)
- Washington Irving – sketch book for Everyman Books (Box 121)
- Travel articles – Sunday Times, etc. (Box 121)
- Clippings – humour sitcom (Box 121)
- Obits and profiles (Box 121)
- Clippings on literary prizes (Box 121)
- Clippings on Contemporary culture/Booker/libraries, etc. (Box 121)
- Clippings on universities, education, (2ff.) (Box 121)
- Clippings on TECS and crime (Box 121)
- UEA/Unversity of Birmingham examinations (Box 121)
- David Lodge (Box 121)
- Greedy/Anglia (Box 121)
- Gravy Train/EEC recent issues (clippings) (Box 121)
- A Mixture of Frailties (film) (Box 121)
- Tamara (TV) (Box 121)
- Inspector Morse (Box 121)
- A Touch of Frost 4/Keys to the car (Box 121)
- A Touch of Frost/Appendix Man (Box 121)
- Imaginary Friends (Box 121)
- Porterhouse Blue – TV version (Box 121)
- Blott on the Landscape – TV version (Box 122)
- Philosopher Traitor (Paul de Man) (Box 122)
- The Vortex – Stagescreen Productions (Box 122)
- Flush – correspondence, etc./faxes (Box 122)
- Flush – film (Box 122)
- Regionalism – Michael Weigall Productions (Box 122)
- Regionality – BBC radio program/Opinion (Box 122)
- Picture Partnership Productions (Box 122)
- Dangerous Pilgrimages – drafting of book (Box 122)
- Lectures – apple and worm, etc. (Box 122)
- American literature and the coming of World War 2 (Berlin) (Box 122)
- Saul Bellow – articles for book (Box 122)
- Saul Bellow's intellectual heroes and other pieces (Box 122)
- Visit to China, 1980 (Box 122)
- China/notes for lectures, etc. (Box 122)
- Various newspaper articles –, 1980s (Box 122)
- Book reviews – Vogue (Box 122)
- Early humour for Punch (Box 122)
- Book reviews for Guardian/1960s on (Box 122)
- UEA/Centres promotion (Box 122)
- Writer's view of fiction (Box 122)
- Inspeak (Pavilion) – Tatler version & ideas (Box 122)
- Inspeak – new ideas (Box 122)
- The university novel – articles & lectures (Box 123)
- The English novel and its social context (Zurich) (Box 123)
- Modern British novel – 1876–1900 (Box 123)
- British novel in the 1930s – 1945, (2ff.) (Box 123)
- Evelyn Waugh (Box 123)
- Ford Maddox Ford lecture (Bologna) and article (Faber) and Ian Fletcher article (Box 123)
- Joyce and Forster – Norwich tapes, etc. (Box 123)
- Turn of the Novel – lecture (Box 123)
- The Introverted Novel (Box 123)
- Graham Greene (Box 123)
- Malcolm Lowry, (2ff.) (Box 123)
- Virginia Woolf, (2ff.) (Box 123)
- History Man – American and foreign reviews (Box 123)
- History Man – reviews/articles about (Box 123)
- Rates of Exchange – British reviews, (2ff.) (Box 124)
- Rates of Exchange – Australian, American and other foreign reviews, (3ff.) (Box 124)
- Pudd'nhead Wilson & Train art. (C.Q.), (2ff.) (Box 124)
- New writing 1 and 2/ British Council (Box 124)
- New writing anthology/ British Council (Box 124)
- Revue stuff for Geoffrey Perkins (Box 124)
- Revue – current (Box 124)
- Secker & Curtis Brown – correspondence over novel and stories (Box 124)
- The Telling Life – literary biography lecture (Box 124)
- Lectures: Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?/Modern American poetry experiment (Box 124)
- Lectures/Booker Prize – British writing in the 80s (Box 124)
- Lectures/modernism – post–modernism/others on postmodernism (Box 124)
- Lectures/British and American 1920s (Box 124)
- Great writers – Virginia Woolf (Box 124)
- The English novel in the 1920s (Box 124)
- American drama (Box 124)
- Early 20th Century American poetry (Box 124)
- American 19th century poetry (Box 124)
- Contemporary American poetry (Box 124)
- American novel, 1930 – Miller, West, etc. (Box 124)
- The American novel in the 1930s, Opus book (Box 124)
- Modern British Novel – Penguin revision (Box 125)
- Saul Bellow – articles on (Box 125)
- Material on literary profession (Box 125)
- King's Lynn Festival material (Box 125)
- The Avant Garde and American Modernism/Venice, (3ff.) (Box 125)
- Post–modernism studies on books, etc., (2ff.) (Box 125)
- Penguin book of modern short stories – reviews (Box 125)
- Slaka book – reviews, etc. (Box 125)
- The Modern World – reviews, etc. (Box 125)
- Mensonge – reviews, etc. (Box 125)
- Longman introduction to American studies (Brabury & Temperley), revised version, 1997 (Box 125)
- Present laughter – comic anthology (Box 125)
- Penguin book of short stories, (3ff.) (Box 125)
- Atlas of literature – planning (Box 125)
- Dangerous Pilgrimages – American reviews (Box 125)
- Dangerous Pilgrimages – reviews, etc. (Box 125)
- Class work – UEA story anthology (Box 125)
- The Modern British Novel – reviews, etc. (Box 125)
- Millennium library – plans of seminar (Box 125)
- Atlas of Literature – drafts of text, renaissance, etc. (Box 125)
- Atlas of literature – versions of scheme (Box 125)
- Atlas of literature – compilations (Box 125)
- Atlas of literature – prelims/etc. (Box 125)
- Broadcasts on Contemporary English Novel (Box 126)
- The novel since 1945 – text and notes, (2ff.) (Box 126)
- The novel today – mss. (Box 126)
- Pemberton Billing (TV) (Box 126)
- Doctor Criminale – adaptation, ZED Productions (Box 126)
- The Green Man – BBC–TV. mostly clippings (Box 126)
- Articles on theory of fiction (Box 126)
- The problem of character (Box 126)
- Modern British writing – book lists, etc. for conferences (Box 126)
- Bibliographies for British Countil tours, etc. (Box 126)
- Doctor Criminale – reviews (Box 126)
- Cuts – reviews (Box 126)
- Rates of Exchange – correspondence about (Box 126)
- Rates of Exchange – inventing Slakan language (Box 126)
- Rates of Exchange – workbooks, notes (Box 126)
- Cuts, (3ff.) (Box 126)
- Miscellaneous papers (Box 126)
- The Spy Club – TV (Box 127)
- Inspector Frost – TV (Box 127)
- Paul de Man – TV (Box 127)
- Cut – Yorkshire TV (Box 127)
- William Faulkner (Box 127)
- John Dos Passos, (2ff.) (Box 127)
- F. Scott Fitzgerald (Box 127)
- Ernest Hemingway (Box 127)
- Fitzgerald/Hemingway (Box 127)
- Saul Bellow – Penguin introduction (Box 127)
- Philip Roth (Box 127)
- John Barth (Box 127)
- Barthelme/Coover (Box 127)
- Gaddis/Gass (Box 127)
- John Hawkes (Box 127)
- Joseph Heller (Box 127)
- Modern American Novel – 1941–1960/versions (Box 127)